A Guide to the Mutual Assurance Society of Virginia Declarations and Revaluations of Assurance, 1796-1966
Library of Virginia
- Mutual Assurance Society of Virginia Declarations and Revaluations of Assurance, 1796-1966.
  - Volume 32 [Declarations 1-33], 1805-1811. (Reel MR 4123, Volume v032)
    New policies and 2 revaluations. Cities: Cartersville (Cumberland), Columbia (Fluvanna), Diuguidsville (Buckingham), Fauquier Court House (Fauquier), Liberty (Bedford), Middlebrook (Augusta), Milton (Albemarle), North Milton (Albemarle), New Canton (Buckingham), New London (Campbell), Occoquan Town (Prince William), Scottsville (Powhatan, #24-25, revaluation), Smithfield (Isle of Wight), Stanardsville (Orange), Stevensburg (Culpeper), Tappahannock (Essex), Urbanna (Middlesex), Warren (Albemarle), Warrington (Fauquier), Waterford (Loudoun).
  - Volume 33 [Declarations 1-121], 1805. (Reel MR 4123, Volume v033)
    New policies and revaluations. Cities: Bernardsburg (Fluvanna), Belfield (Greensvile), Brownsburgh (Rockbridge), Ca Ira (Cumberland), Cartersville (Cumberland), Centerville (Fairfax), Columbia (Fluvanna), Diuguidsville (Buckingham), Dunkirk (King & Queen), Fairfax (Culpeper), Fairfield (Rockbridge), Farmville (Prince Edward), Fauquier Court House (Fauquier), Greensville (Augusta), Hay Market (Prince William), Hillsboro (Loudoun), Jefferson (Powhatan), Liberty (Bedford), Lloyds (Essex), Milton (Albemarle), New Canton (Buckingham), New London (Campbell), Port Conway (King George), Port Royal (Caroline), Richmond (Henrico), Scottsville (Powhatan), Stevensburg (Culpeper), Tappahannock (Essex), Urbanna (Middlesex), Warren (Albemarle), Washington (Culpeper), Waterford (Loudoun), Yanceyville (Louisa).
  - Volume 34 [Declarations 122-201], 1805-1811. (Reel MR 4124, Volume v034)
    Revaluations. Cities: Bath (Berkeley), Brownsburgh (Rockbridge), Ca Ira (Buckingham), Ca Ira (Cumberland), Cartersville (Cumberland), Charles Town (Jefferson), Clementown (Amelia), Danville (Pittsylvania), Fairfax (Culpeper), Front Royal (Frederick), Gatesville (Chesterfield), Jefferson (Culpeper), Madison (Madison), Middlebrook (Augusta), Middletown (Berkeley), Milton (Albemarle), New Canton (Buckingham), Newcastle (Hanover), New London (Campbell), New Market (Shenandoah), New York (Albemarle), Occoquan Town (Prince William), Port Royal (Caroline), Stanardsville (Orange), Stephensburg (Frederick), Tappahannock (Essex), Waynesboro (Augusta), Warren (Albemarle), Yorktown (York).
  - Volume 35 [Declarations 1-273], 1805. (Reel MR 4124, Volume v035)
    Revaluations. Counties: Albemarle, Amelia, Buckingham, Chesterfield, Culpeper, Cumberland, Dinwiddie, Essex, Fairfax, Fauquier, King & Queen, Loudoun, Louisa, Middlesex, Norfolk, Nottoway, Orange, Powhatan, Prince William, Rockingham, Spotsylvania.
  - Volume 36 [Declarations 274-528],1805. (Reel MR 4124, Volume v036)
    Revaluations. Counties: Albemarle, Amelia, Amherst, Brunswick, Buckingham, Caroline, Chesterfield, Culpeper, Cumberland, Dinwiddie, Essex, Fluvanna, Gloucester, Greensville, Louisa, Lunenburg, Mecklenburg, Orange, Powhatan, Prince Edward, Spotsylvania, Sussex.
  - Volume 37 [Declarations 529-770],1805. (Reel MR 4124, Volume v037)
    Revaluations. Counties: Accomack, Amelia, Augusta, Bedford, Buckingham, Campbell, Caroline, Chesterfield, Culpeper, Essex, Fauquier, Frederick, Gloucester, Goochland, Hanover, Henrico, King & Queen, King George, King William, Lancaster, Loudoun, Mecklenburg, Northampton, Orange, Prince George, Prince William, Richmond, Rockbridge, Rockingham, Spotsylvania, Stafford, Westmoreland.
  - Volume 38 [Declarations 771-942],1805. (Reel MR 4124, Volume v038)
    Revaluations. Counties: Albemarle, Amherst, Augusta, Bedford, Berkeley, Buckingham, Campbell, Caroline, Charlotte, Cumberland, Essex, Franklin, Frederick, Gloucester, Goochland, Halifax, Jefferson, Loudoun, Orange, Pittsylvania, Prince Edward, Westmoreland.
  - Volume 39 [Declarations 943-1107],1805-1806. (Reel MR 4124, Volume v039)
    Revaluations. Counties: Amelia, Bedford, Berkeley, Botetourt, Brunswick, Buckingham, Caroline, Charles City, Chesterfield, Culpeper, Cumberland, Fluvanna, Frederick, Goochland, Hanover, Henrico, James City, Jefferson, King George, King William, Louisa, Madison, Orange, Prince Edward, Rockbridge, Spotsylvania, Stafford, Surry, York.
  - Volume 40 [Declarations 1108-1211],1806-1808. (Reel MR 4124, Volume v040)
    Revaluations. Counties: Accomack, Albemarle, Amherst, Berkeley, Botetourt, Caroline, Charlotte, Chesterfield, Culpeper, Cumberland, Dinwiddie, Fluvanna, Frederick, Gloucester, Goochland, Henrico, James City, Jefferson, Loudoun, Mathews, Nansemond, Norfolk, Northampton, Orange, Pittsylvania, Spotsylvania, Stafford, Sussex, Westmoreland.
  - Volume 41 [Declarations 1212-1279],1808-1811. (Reel MR 4124, Volume v041)
    Revaluations. Counties: Albemarle, Buckingham, Caroline, Chesterfield, Essex, Fauquier, Goochland, Hanover, Henrico, Isle of Wight, James City, King & Queen, Louisa, Lunenburg, Nansemond, New Kent, Norfolk, Orange, Powhatan, Prince Edward, Prince George, Prince William, Spotsylvania, Stafford, York.
  - Volume 42 [Declarations 1280-1545], 1812-1815. (Reel MR 4124, Volume v042)
    Revaluations. Counties: Albemarle, Amelia, Buckingham, Charlotte, Chesterfield, Cumberland, Gloucester, Goochland, Halifax, Hanover, Henrico, Isle of Wight, King William, Loudoun, Louisa, Nansemond, Nelson, Orange, Pittsylvania, Powhatan, Prince Edward, Princess Anne, Rockbridge, Spotsylvania, Stafford.
  - Volume 43 [Declarations 1546-1945],1814-1816. (Reel MR 4125, Volume v043)
    Revaluations. Counties: Amelia, Amherst, Berkeley, Buckingham, Campbell, Charlotte, Chesterfield, Cumberland, Dinwiddie, Fairfax, Gloucester, Goochland, Hanover, Henrico, Jefferson, King & Queen, Loudoun, Louisa, Mathews, Middlesex, Orange, Pittsylvania, Powhatan, Prince Edward, Spotsylvania.
  - Volume 44 [Declarations 1946-2145], 1816. (Reel MR 4125, Volume v044)
    Revaluations. Counties: Caroline, Charles City, Chesterfield, Culpeper, Cumberland, Dinwiddie, Essex, Gloucester, Goochland, Greensville, Hanover, Henrico, James City, King & Queen, King George, King William, Louisa, Madison, Mecklenburg, Nottoway, Orange, Prince Edward, Prince William, Stafford, Westmoreland.
  - Volume 45 [Declarations 2146-2345],1816-1817. (Reel MR 4125, Volume v045)
    Revaluations. Counties: Albemarle, Augusta, Bedford, Brunswick, Campbell, Caroline, Chesterfield, Culpeper, Dinwiddie, Fluvanna, Hanover, King William, Lancaster, Loudoun, Mecklenburg, Nelson, Orange, Prince Edward, Prince George, Richmond, Rockbridge, Spotsylvania, Stafford, Westmoreland.
  - Volume 46 [Declarations 501-589, 2346-2452], 1816-1819. (Reel MR 4125, Volume v046)
    New policies (501-589). Revaluations (2346-2452). Counties: Albemarle, Amelia, Augusta, Bedford, Berkeley, Brunswick, Buckingham, Campbell, Caroline, Chesterfield, Culpeper, Cumberland, Dinwiddie, Essex, Fauquier, Frederick, Gloucester, Goochland, Hanover, Henrico, Isle of Wight, James City, Jefferson, King & Queen, King George, King William, Loudoun, Louisa, Lunenburg, Madison, Mathews, Mecklenburg, Nansemond, New Kent, Norfolk, Nottoway, Orange, Powhatan, Prince George, Princess Anne, Rockbridge, Spotsylvania, Stafford, Sussex.
  - Volume 47 [Declarations 336-405],1808-1811. (Reel MR 4125, Volume v047)
    New policies. Counties: Albemarle, Botetourt, Buckingham, Campbell, Caroline, Charles City, Chesterfield, Culpeper, Cumberland, Fairfax, Fauquier, Goochland, Hanover, Hampshire, Henrico, Isle of Wight, Louisa, Norfolk, Powhatan, Prince Edward, Prince George, Rockbridge, Spotsylvania, Stafford, Sussex.
  - Volume 48 [Declarations 406-500], 1809-1816. (Reel MR 4126, Volume v048)
    New policies. Counties: Albemarle, Amelia, Amherst, Augusta, Berkeley, Buckingham, Campbell, Caroline, Charles City, Chesterfield, Culpeper, Cumberland, Dinwiddie, Fairfax, Fauquier, Gloucester, Goochland, Hanover, King & Queen, Louisa, Madison, Mathews, Nansemond, Nelson, Orange, Powhatan, Prince Edward, Richmond, Spotsylvania, Stafford.
  - Volume 49 [Declarations 1-103], 1805-1806. (Reel MR 4126, Volume v049)
    New policies. Cities: Alexandria, Blandford (Prince George), Charlottesville (Albemarle), Dumfries (Prince William), Falmouth (Stafford), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Leesburg (Loudoun), Manchester (Chesterfield), Martinsburg (Berkeley), Norfolk (Norfolk), Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Portsmouth (Norfolk), Richmond (Henrico), Shepherdstown (Jefferson), Staunton (Augusta), Williamsburg (James City #103), Winchester (Frederick).
  - Volume 50 [Declarations 104-170],1806-1808. (Reel MR 4126, Volume v050)
    New policies. Cities: Alexandria, Falmouth (Stafford), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Manchester (Chesterfield), Norfolk (Norfolk), Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Portsmouth (Norfolk), Richmond (Henrico), Winchester (Frederick).
  - Volume 51 [Declarations 171-266],1808-1811. (Reel MR 4126, Volume v051)
    New policies. Cities: Alexandria, Falmouth (Stafford), Fincastle (Botetourt), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Manchester (Chesterfield), Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Portsmouth (Norfolk), Richmond (Henrico).
  - Volume 52 [Declarations 267-500],1812-1815. (Reel MR 4126, Volume v052)
    New policies. Cities: Blandford (Prince George), Charlottesville (Albemarle), Dumfries (Prince William), Fairfax (Culpeper), Falmouth (Stafford), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Jamestown (Prince Edward), Leesburg (Loudoun), Lexington (Rockbridge), Lynchburg (Campbell), Manchester (Chesterfield), Milton (Albemarle), Norfolk (Norfolk), Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Petersburg suburb (Prince George), Portsmouth (Norfolk), Richmond (Henrico), Staunton (Augusta), Stevensburg (Culpeper), Suffolk (Nansemond), Tappahannock (Essex), Warrenton (Fauquier), Williamsburg (James City and York).
  - Volume 53 [Declarations 501-700],1815-1816. (Reel MR 4126, Volume v053)
    New policies. Cities: Blandford (Prince George), Boydton (Mecklenburg), Cartersville (Cumberland), Charlottesville (Albemarle), Fairfax (Culpeper), Falmouth (Stafford), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Liberty (Bedford), Lynchburg (Campbell), Norfolk (Norfolk), Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Portsmouth (Norfolk), Richmond (Henrico), Stanardsville (Orange).
  - Volume 54 [Declarations 701-900], 1816-1817. (Reel MR 4126, Box b01)
    New policies. Cities: Falmouth (Stafford), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Ghent (Norfolk), Jerusalem (Southampton), Liberty (Bedford), Manchester (Chesterfield), Norfolk (Norfolk), Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Petersburg suburb (Chesterfield), Port Royal (Caroline), Portsmouth (Norfolk), Richmond (Henrico), Stanardsville (Orange), Staunton (Augusta), Suffolk (Nansemond), Williamsburg (York), Yorktown (York).
  - Volume 55 [Declarations 901-1200], 1817-1818. (Reel MR 4126, Box b01)
    New policies. Cities: Blandford (Prince George), Falmouth (Stafford), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Gosport (Norfolk), Jamestown (Prince Edward), Madison (Madison), Manchester (Chesterfield), Norfolk (Norfolk), Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Portsmouth (Norfolk), Richmond (Henrico), Stevensburg (Culpeper), Tappahannock (Essex), Warrenton (Fauquier), Washington (Culpeper), Yorktown (York).
  - Volume 56 [Declarations 1201-1400], 1816-1819. (Reel MR 4127, Box b02)
    New policies. Cities: Blandford (Prince George), Falmouth (Stafford), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Hampton (Elizabeth City), Lynchburg (Campbell), Manchester (Chesterfield), Norfolk (Norfolk), Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Portsmouth (Norfolk), Richmond (Henrico).
  - Volume 57 [Declarations 1401-1663], 1819-1821. (Reel MR 4127, Box b02)
    New policies. Cities: Blandford (Prince George), Fairfax (Culpeper), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Gosport (Norfolk), Lexington (Rockbridge), Lynchburg (Campbell), Manchester (Chesterfield), Middletown (Berkeley), Norfolk (Norfolk), Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Portsmouth (Norfolk), Richmond (Henrico), Staunton (Augusta), Warrenton (Fauquier), Williamsburg (James City), Yorktown (York).
  - Volume 58 [Declarations 1A-300A], 1845-1850. (Reel MR 4127, Box b03)
    New policies. Cities: Alexandria, Charles Town (Jefferson), Charlottesville (Albemarle), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Front Royal (Warren), Leesburg (Loudoun), Lexington (Rockbridge), Lynchburg (Campbell), Martinsburg (Berkeley), Norfolk (Norfolk), Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Petersburg suburb (Chesterfield), Portsmouth (Norfolk), Richmond (Henrico), Smithfield (Isle of Wight), Staunton (Augusta), Suffolk (Nansemond), Warrenton (Fauquier), Williamsburg (York), Winchester (Frederick).
  - Volume 59 [Declarations 301A-600A],1850-1854. (Reel MR 4127, Box b03)
    New policies. Cities: Alexandria, Charlottesville (Albemarle), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Hampton (Elizabeth City), Leesburg (Loudoun), Lynchburg (Campbell), Manchester (Chesterfield), Martinsburg (Berkeley), Middleburg (Loudoun), Norfolk (Norfolk), Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Petersburg suburb (Chesterfield), Pocahontas (Chesterfield), Port Royal (Caroline), Portsmouth (Norfolk), Richmond (Henrico), Smithfield (Isle of Wight), Staunton (Augusta), Warrenton (Fauquier), Williamsburg (York), Winchester (Frederick).
  - Volume 60 [Declarations 601A-924A],1854-1866. (Reel MR 4127, Box b04)
    New policies. Cities: Blandford (Prince George), Charlottesville (Albemarle), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Hampton (Elizabeth City), Leesburg (Loudoun), Lexington (Rockbridge), Lynchburg (Campbell), Manchester (Chesterfield), Martinsburg (Berkeley), Norfolk (Norfolk), Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Portsmouth (Norfolk), Richmond (Henrico), Smithfield (Isle of Wight), Staunton (Augusta), Suffolk (Nansemond), Tappahannock (Essex), Warrenton (Fauquier), Williamsburg (York).
  - Volume 61 [Declarations 1-249], 1805. (Reel MR 4128, Box b04)
    Revaluations. Cities: Alexandria, Blandford (Prince George), Charlottesville (Albemarle), Dumfries (Prince William), Falmouth (Stafford), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Leesburg (Loudoun), Lynchburg (Campbell), Manchester (Chesterfield), Norfolk (Norfolk), Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Richmond (Henrico).
  - Volume 62 [Declarations 250-416], 1805-1807. (Reel MR 4128, Box b05)
    Revaluations. Cities: Alexandria, Charlottesville (Albemarle), Dumfries (Prince William), Falmouth (Stafford), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Harrisonburg (Rockingham), Lexington (Rockbridge), Manchester (Chesterfield), Norfolk (Norfolk), Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Portsmouth (Norfolk), Richmond (Henrico).
  - Volume 63 [Declarations 417-554],1805-1806. (Reel MR 4128, Box b05)
    Revaluations. Cities: Alexandria, Blandford (Prince George), Charlottesville (Albemarle), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Lexington (Rockbridge), Manchester (Chesterfield), Norfolk (Norfolk), Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Pocahontas (Chesterfield), Richmond (Henrico), Staunton (Augusta), Woodstock (Shenandoah).
  - Volume 64 [Declarations 555-760],1805-1806. (Reel MR 4128, Box b06)
    Revaluations. Cities: Alexandria, Blandford (Prince George), Charles Town (Jefferson), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Hampton (Elizabeth City), Leesburg (Loudoun), Lexington (Rockbridge), Manchester (Chesterfield), Martinsburg (Berkeley), Norfolk (Norfolk), Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Portsmouth (Norfolk), Richmond (Henrico), Shepherdstown (Jefferson), Staunton (Augusta), Suffolk (Nansemond), Williamsburg (James City), Williamsburg (York), Winchester (Frederick).
  - Volume 65 [Declarations 761-905], 1805-1808. (Reel MR 4128, Volume v065)
    Revaluations. Cities: Alexandria, Charlottesville (Albemarle), Falmouth (Stafford), Fincastle (Botetourt), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Lynchburg (Campbell), Manchester (Chesterfield), Martinsburg (Berkeley), Norfolk (Norfolk), Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Portsmouth (Norfolk), Richmond (Henrico), Shepherdstown (Jefferson), Staunton (Augusta), Winchester (Frederick).
  - Volume 66 [Declarations 906-1055], 1808-1811. (Reel MR 4128, Box b07)
    Revaluations. Cities: Charlottesville (Albemarle), Falmouth (Stafford), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Lynchburg (Campbell), Manchester (Chesterfield), Norfolk (Norfolk), Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Richmond (Henrico), Williamsburg (James City), Williamsburg (York).
  - Volume 67 [Declarations 1056-1117], 1811. (Reel MR 4128, Box b07)
    Revaluations. Cities: Blandford (Prince George), Charlottesville (Albemarle), Falmouth (Stafford), Fincastle (Botetourt), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Hampton (Elizabeth City), Lynchburg (Campbell), Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Pocahontas (Chesterfield), Richmond (Henrico), Staunton (Augusta), Suffolk (Nansemond), Sussex City (Prince George), Williamsburg (James City), Williamsburg (York).
  - Volume 68 [Declarations 1118-1400], 1812-1815. (Reel MR 4128, Box b08)
    Revaluations. Cities: Alexandria, Cartersville (Cumberland), Falmouth (Stafford), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Jefferson (Powhatan), Leesburg (Loudoun), Lexington (Rockbridge), Lynchburg (Campbell), Madison (Madison), Manchester (Chesterfield), New Canton (Buckingham), Norfolk (Norfolk), Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Portsmouth (Norfolk), Richmond (Henrico), Scottsville (Powhatan), Smithfield (Isle of Wight), Staunton (Augusta), Stevensburg (Culpeper), Suffolk (Nansemond), Tappahannock (Essex), Warminister (Nelson), Warrenton (Fauquier), Williamsburg (York).
  - Volume 69 [Declarations 1401-1700],1814-1815. (Reel MR 4129, Box b08)
    Revaluations. Cities: Alexandria, Blandford (Prince George), Ca Ira (Cumberland), Cartersville (Cumberland), Clementown (Amelia), Danville (Pittsylvania), Falmouth (Stafford), Farmville (Prince Edward), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Manchester (Chesterfield), Martinsburgh (Berkeley), Norfolk (Norfolk), Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Portsmouth (Norfolk), Richmond (Henrico), Scottsville (Powhatan), Williamsburg (James City), Williamsburg (York), Yanceyville (Louisa), Yorktown (York).
  - Volume 70 [Declarations 1701-1900], 1815. (Reel MR 4129, Box b09)
    Revaluations. Cities: Alexandria, Centreville (Fairfax), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Martinsburgh (Berkeley), Middletown (Berkeley), Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Richmond (Henrico), Williamsburg (James City), Williamsburg (York).
  - Volume 71 [Declarations 1901-2100], 1815-1816. (Reel MR 4129, Box b09)
    Revaluations. Cities: Alexandria, Belefield (Greensville), Blandford (Prince George), Boydton (Mecklenburg), Danville (Pittsylvania), Diuguidsville (Buckingham), Dunkirk (King & Queen), Fairfax (Culpeper), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Glasgow (Amherst), Madison (Madison), Manchester (Chesterfield), New London (Campbell), Norfolk (Norfolk), Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Port Royal (Caroline), Richmond (Henrico), Shepherdstown (Jefferson), Standardsville (Orange), Stevensburg (Culpeper), Tappahannock (Essex), Urbanna (Middlesex), Williamsburg (York).
  - Volume 72 [Declarations 2101-2300], 1816-1817. (Reel MR 4129, Box b10)
    Revaluations. Cities: Belefield (Greensville), Blandford (Prince George), Brownsburg (Rockbridge), Charlestown (Jefferson), Columbia (Fluvanna), Dumfries (Prince William), Fairfax (Culpeper), Falmouth (Stafford), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Greensville (Augusta), Hampton (Elizabeth City), Harrisborough (Augusta), Hicksford (Greensville), Hillsborough (Loudoun), Leesburg (Loudoun), Lexington (Rockbridge), Liberty (Bedford), Lynchburg (Campbell), Manchester (Chesterfield), Martinsburgh (Berkeley), Middlebrook (Augusta), Norfolk (Norfolk), Occoquan (Prince William), Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Port Conway (King George), Portsmouth (Norfolk), Richmond (Henrico), Scottsville (Powhatan), Shepherdstown (Jefferson), Staunton (Augusta), Warminister (Nelson), Warren (Albemarle), Washington (Culpeper), Waterford (Loudoun), Winchester (Frederick).
  - Volume 73 [Declarations 2301-2500], 1816-1818. (Reel MR 4129, Box b10)
    Revaluations. Cities: Alexandria, Bath (Berkeley), Blandford (Prince George), Charlottesville (Albemarle), Falmouth (Stafford), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Jerusalem (Southampton), Leesburg (Loudoun), Lexington (Rockbridge), Madison (Madison), Manchester (Chesterfield), Norfolk (Norfolk), Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Portsmouth (Norfolk), Richmond (Henrico), Shepherdstown (Jefferson), Smithfield (Isle of Wight), Staunton (Augusta), Stevensburg (Culpeper), Suffolk (Nansemond), Warrenton (Fauquier), Washington (Culpeper), Williamsburg (James City), Williamsburg (York), Winchester (Frederick).
  - Volume 74 [Declarations 2501-2750], 1816-1820. (Reel MR 4130, Box b11)
    Revaluations. Cities: Berryville (Frederick), Blandford (Prince George), Charlottesville (Albemarle), Culpeper Court House (Culpeper), Falmouth (Stafford), Fincastle (Botetourt), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Lexington (Rockbridge), Madison (Madison), Manchester (Chesterfield), Martinsburgh (Berkeley), Norfolk (Norfolk), Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Pocahontas (Chesterfield, Petersburg suburb), Portsmouth (Norfolk), Richmond (Henrico), Staunton (Augusta), Stephensburg (Frederick), Williamsburg (James City), Williamsburg (York), Winchester (Frederick).
  - Volume 75 [Declarations 2751-3050], 1815 (#2832), 1820-1822. (Reel MR 4130, Box b11)
    New policies and revaluations. Cities: Blandford (Prince George), Boydton (Mecklenburg), Chatham (Stafford), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Gosport (Norfolk, Portsmouth suburb), Hampton (Elizabeth City), Harrisonburg (Rockingham), Lexington (Rockbridge), Manchester (Chesterfield), Norfolk (Norfolk), Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Petersburg suburbs (Chesterfield and Prince George), Portsmouth (Norfolk), Richmond (Henrico), Suffolk (Nansemond), Warrenton (Fauquier), Williamsburg (James City).
  - Volume 76 [Declarations 3051-3250], 1822. (Reel MR 4130, Box b12)
    Revaluations. Cities: Blandford (Prince George), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Norfolk, Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Petersburg suburb (Prince George), Powhatan Court House (Powhatan), Scottsville (Powhatan).
  - Volume 77 [Declarations 3251-3450], 1822. (Reel MR 4130, Box b12)
    Revaluations. Cities: Blandford (Prince George), Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Petersburg suburb (Prince George), Pocahontas (Chesterfield).
  - Volume 78 [Declarations 3451-3750], 1822-1831. (Reel MR 4130, Box b13)
    New policies. Revaluations (#3605, Richmond; #3607, Fredericksburg). Cities: Blandford (Prince George), Charlestown (Jefferson), Charlottesville (Albemarle), Dumfries (Prince William), Fairfax (Culpeper), Falmouth (Stafford), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Gosport (Norfolk, suburb of Portsmouth), Hampton (Elizabeth City), Lexington (Rockbridge), Lynchburg (Campbell), Martinsburg (Berkeley), Middleburg (Loudoun), Norfolk (Norfolk), Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Petersburg suburb (Prince George), Portsmouth (Norfolk), Richmond (Henrico), Scottsville (Powhatan), Smithfield (Isle of Wight), Suffolk (Nansemond), Warrenton (Fauquier), Winchester (Frederick).
  - Volume 79 [Declarations 3751-4000], 1822 (1827-#3798). (Reel MR 4131, Box b13)
    Revaluations. Cities: Blandford (Prince George, suburb of Petersburg), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Gosport (Norfolk, suburb of Portsmouth), Martinsburgh (Berkeley), Norfolk, Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Pocahontas (Chesterfield, suburb of Petersburg), Portsmouth (Norfolk), Richmond (Henrico), Suffolk (Nansemond).
  - Volume 80 [Declarations 4001-4300], 1822. (Reel MR 4131, Box b14)
    Revaluations. Cities: Brownsburg (Rockbridge), Falmouth (Stafford), Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Garrards Town or Middletown (Berkeley), Gosport (Norfolk, suburb of Portsmouth), Lexington (Rockbridge), Lynchburg (Campbell), Martinsburg (Berkeley), Middletown or Garrards Town (Berkeley), New London (Campbell), Norfolk, Petersburg (Dinwiddie), Portsmouth (Norfolk), Staunton (Augusta), Suffolk (Nansemond).
  - Volume 81 [Declarations 4301-4600], 1822. (Reel MR 4131, Box b14)
    Revaluations. Cities: Fredericksburg (Spotsylvania), Richmond (Henrico), Smithfield (Isle of Wight), Suffolk (Nansemond).